

# **Arda ERBAHARLI**

in LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/arda-erbaharli-5401471aa/

Github: <a href="https://github.com/ardaerbaharli/">https://github.com/ardaerbaharli/</a>

Portfolio: <a href="https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/">https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/</a>

**Website:** https://ardaerbaharli.github.io

• Home: Ankara (Türkiye)

### **ABOUT ME**

I have been actively engaged in software development for over four years, specializing in the creation of mobile games using the C# programming language. Over the past three years, my primary focus has been on game development, allowing me to gain extensive experience in this field. Since December 2021, I have been working as a freelance game developer, collaborating on numerous projects including various genres, primarily targeting mobile platforms.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Freelance Game Developer**

**Upwork** [ 01/12/2021 - Current ]

As a Top Rated Plus Freelance Game Developer at Upwork, I've been collaborating on numerous projects across the world, primarily targeting mobile platforms. I've worked on hyper casual, puzzle, educational, endless runners, trivia, card games and many more.

### **Game Developer Intern**

**ARD Grup** [ 15/08/2022 - 12/09/2022 ]

**City:** Ankara **Country:** Türkiye

I have developed 3 hyper-casual game clones.

- <u>Globo Run</u> (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio#globoRun) => This is a 3D endless runner game where the player tries to avoid obstacles whilst the player speed increase
- <u>Helix Jump</u> (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/small-games#helixJump )=> Clone of the popular game Helix Jump.
- <u>Arrow Throw (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio/small-games#arrowThrow)</u> => Clone of the popular game Easter Egg Toss.

### **Game Developer Intern**

ARD Bilişim [ 31/05/2021 - 27/06/2021 ]

City: Ankara Country: Türkiye

I have developed a classic Solitaire game with Unity from scratch. You can see <a href="here">here</a> (https://ardaerbaharli.github.io/portfolio#solitaire). Also helped with the implementation of a 3rd party package.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### **Computer Enginner**

**Başkent University** [ 22/09/2018 - 06/07/2023 ]

City: Ankara Country: Türkiye

Website: www.baskent.edu.tr

# **Game Development Trainee**

Google Oyun ve Uygulama Akademisi [ 01/12/2022 – Current ]

Website: https://oyunveuygulamaakademisi.com

#### **Trainee**

**Panteon** [ 01/10/2022 - 01/02/2023 ]

Website: <a href="https://www.panteon.games/akademi/">https://www.panteon.games/akademi/</a>

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

### **English**

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

# **DIGITAL SKILLS**

# **Tools & Technology**

.NET Framework / Version Control System (Git) / Adobe Photoshop / .NET Core / Git / Unity

# **Programming Languages**

C#